United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners. Local 187 (Geneva, NY) Records on Microfilm 5686 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners. Local 187 (Geneva, NY) Records on Microfilm
1901-1964
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America (UBC)
5686 mf
0.56 cubic feet
5 microfilm reels
Records (documents), audiovisual materials, microfilm.
Minute books, dues books, and correspondence
3338525
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, September 26, 2012
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 27, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, better known as the United Brotherhood of Carpenters (UBC).
It was founded in 1881 by Peter J. McGuire and Gustav Luebkert. UBC is one of the largest trade unions in the United States and with its chapters and locals there is an international cooperation that gives it a global role.
Scope and Contents
A negative copy is available upon request.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5718: Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners Documents 5718 mf: Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners Documents on Microfilm 5818 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners Local 662 (Mt. Morris, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5822 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America District Council, Rochester, NY. Records on Microfilm 5810: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 125 (Utica, NY) Records 5810 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 125 (Utica, NY) Records on Microfilm 5819 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 1508 (Lyons, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5820 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 240 (East Rochester, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5828: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 3211 (Herkimer, NY) Minute Books 5828 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 3211 (Herkimer, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5826: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 337 (Whitesboro, NY) Minute Books 5826 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 337 (Whitesboro, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5817 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 502 (Canandaigua, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5821 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 72 (Rochester, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5827: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Mohawk Valley District Council of Carpenters Minute Books 5827 mf: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Mohawk Valley District Council of Carpenters Minute Books on Microfilm
Carpenters--Labor unions--New York (State)--Geneva; United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America. Local 187 (Geneva, N.Y.); United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America.
3338525
- Minutebooks, Vol.1-5 (1907-1937) (Reel 1)
  - Vol. 1: Minute book, 1907-1911; 1 (Reel 1)
  - Vol. 2: Minute book, 1921-1925; 2 (Reel 1)
  - Vol. 3: Minute book, 1926-1933; 3 (Reel 1)
  - Vol. 4: Minute book, 1933-1938; 4 (Reel 1)
  - Vol. 5: Minute book, 1935-1937; 5 (Reel 1)
- Minutebooks, Vol.6-12 (1939-1959) (Reel 2)
  - Vol. 6: Minute book, 1939-1943; 1 (Reel 2)
  - Vol. 7: Minute book, 1943-1948; 2 (Reel 2)
  - Vol. 8: Minute book, 1949-1951; 3 (Reel 2)
  - Vol. 9: Minute book, 1949-1954; 4 (Reel 2)
  - Vol. 10: Minute book, 1951-1952; 5 (Reel 2)
  - Vol. 11: Minute book, 1954-1957; 6 (Reel 2)
  - Vol. 12: Minute book, 1957-1959; 7 (Reel 2)
- Minutebooks, Vol.13 (1960-1965); Correspondence, Vol.14 (1926-1937); Dues Books, Vol.15-21 (1901-1914) (Reel 3)
  - Vol. 13: Minute book, 1960-1964; 1 (Reel 3)
  - Vol. 14: Correspondence, 1926-1937; 2 (Reel 3)
  - Vol. 15: Dues Book, 1901-1902; 3 (Reel 3)
  - Vol. 16: Dues Book, 1903-1906; 4 (Reel 3)
  - Vol. 17: Dues Book, 1907-1909; 5 (Reel 3)
  - Vol. 18: Dues Book, 1910; 6 (Reel 3)
  - Vol. 19: Dues Book, 1911; 7 (Reel 3)
  - Vol. 20: Dues Book, 1912; 8 (Reel 3)
  - Vol. 21: Dues Book, 1913-1914; 9 (Reel 3)
- Dues Books, Vol. 22-25 (1915-1932) (Reel 4)
  - Vol. 22: Dues Book, 1915-1916; 1 (Reel 4)
  - Vol. 23: Dues Book, 1919-1922; 2 (Reel 4)
  - Vol. 24: Dues Book, 1923-1926; 3 (Reel 4)
  - Vol. 25: Dues Book, 1927-1932; 4 (Reel 4)
- Dues Books, Vol. 26-30 (1932-1949) (Reel 5)
  - Vol. 26: Dues Book, 1932-1933; 1 (Reel 5)
  - Vol. 27: Dues Book, 1933-1938; 2 (Reel 5)
  - Vol. 28: Dues Book, 1934-1937; 3 (Reel 5)
  - Vol. 29: Dues Book, 1943; 4 (Reel 5)
  - Vol. 30: Dues Book, 1947-1949; 5 (Reel 5)